<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dominik Wehr</title>
    <link>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dominik Wehr</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://dowehr.dortselb.st/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bachelor&#39;s Thesis</title>
      <link>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/bachelors_thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/bachelors_thesis/</guid>
      <description>Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Thesis I wrote my Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s thesis at the Programming Systems Lab at Saarland university, advised by Dominik Kirst, and Yannick Forster and supervised by Gert Smolka. Broadly, the thesis dealt with completeness proofs of first-order logic in a constructive setting, more specifically the type theory of Coq which was used to mechanize all of thesis&#39; results.
The thesis can be roughly split into two halves. The first half is concerned with the ∀,→,⊥-fragment of first-order logic, both over Tarski and Kripke models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dominik Wehr</title>
      <link>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me  I am a PhD student at the Logic Group at Gothenburg University supervised by Graham Leigh and Bahareh Afshari. My research lies in the area of cyclic proof theory with specific interest in the soundness conditions of cyclic derivation systems. More generally, I am interested in the exploration of reasonably strong foundational systems (i.e. at least an arithmetic) by means of proof theory and the methods of (constructive) reverse mathematics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Masters&#39;s thesis</title>
      <link>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/masters_thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/masters_thesis/</guid>
      <description>Master&amp;rsquo;s thesis I wrote this thesis under the supervision of Bahareh Afshari to obtain my Master of Logic. Broadly, the thesis is concerned with capturing the structural (i.e. non-logical) properties common to cyclic derivation systems in a categorical manner.
Abstract Cyclic derivations are finite graphs in which adjacent nodes are labeled by sequents according to locally sound derivation rules. These graphs serve as a finite representation of the infinite derivation trees obtained by unraveling them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/projects/</guid>
      <description>Research Projects The Master of Logic allows students to earn up to 24 EC via research projects. These are the research projects I have worked on so far.
 Formal Analysis of Material Dialogues for FOL This project was supervised by Dominik Kirst from Saarland University. It can be viewed as me carrying out one of the ideas mentioned in the &amp;ldquo;future work&amp;rdquo; section of my Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s thesis. Dialogical logic, originally put forward by Paul Lorenzen, captures the notion of first-order validity in terms of games modeled after a debate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Teaching At University of Amsterdam, I was a student TA for the following courses:
   Year Course     Spring 2021 Proof Theory    At Saarland University, I was a student TA for the following courses:
   Year Course     Winter 2017 Programming 1   Summer 2018 Introduction to Computational Logic   Summer 2019 Introduction to Computational Logic    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
