<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dominik Wehr</title>
    <link>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dominik Wehr</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://dowehr.dortselb.st/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bachelor&#39;s Thesis</title>
      <link>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/bachelors_thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/bachelors_thesis/</guid>
      <description>A Constructive Analysis of First-Order Completeness Theorems in Coq Type: Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s thesis
Advisors: Dominik Kirst and Yannick Forster
Supervisor: Gert Smolka
Institution: Saarland University, Programming Systems Lab
Digital copy: Available here
Coq mechanization: CoqDoc and github
Resulting Publications Completeness Theorems for First-Order Logic Analysed in Constructive Type Theory [Preprint]
Yannick Forster, Dominik Kirst, Dominik Wehr
LFCS 2020, Deerfield Beach, Florida, USA, 2020. Completeness Theorems for First-Order Logic Analysed in Constructive Type Theory: Extended Version [Preprint]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dominik Wehr</title>
      <link>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a PhD student at the Logic Group at Gothenburg University supervised by Graham Leigh and Bahareh Afshari. My research lies in the area of cyclic proof theory with specific interest in the soundness conditions of cyclic derivation systems. More generally, I am interested in the exploration of reasonably strong foundational systems (i.e. at least an arithmetic) by means of proof theory and the methods of (constructive) reverse mathematics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Licentiate thesis</title>
      <link>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/licentiate_thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/licentiate_thesis/</guid>
      <description>Representation Matters in Cyclic Proof Theory Type: Licentiate thesis
Supervisors: Graham E. Leigh and Bahareh Afshari
Institution: University of Gothenburg
Digital copy: Available on GUPEA
Abstract Cyclic proof systems allow derivations whose underlying structure is a finite graph, rather than a well-founded tree. The soundness of cyclic proofs is usually ensured by imposing additional conditions beyond well-formedness. Distinct cyclic representations of the same logic can be obtained by combining the same stock of logical rules with different soundness conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Masters&#39;s thesis</title>
      <link>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/masters_thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/masters_thesis/</guid>
      <description>An Abstract Framework for the Analysis of Cyclic Derivations Type: Master&amp;rsquo;s thesis
Supervisor: Bahareh Afshari
Institution: University of Amsterdam, Institute for Logic, Language and Computation
Digital copy: Available on the ILLC eprints server
Resulting publication Abstract Cyclic Proofs
Bahareh Afshari, Dominik Wehr
WoLLIC 2022, Iaşi, Romania, 2022. Abstract Cyclic derivations are finite graphs in which adjacent nodes are labeled by sequents according to locally sound derivation rules. These graphs serve as a finite representation of the infinite derivation trees obtained by unraveling them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/projects/</guid>
      <description>Research Projects The Master of Logic allows students to earn up to 24 EC via research projects. These are the research projects I have worked on so far.
Formal Analysis of Material Dialogues for FOL This project was supervised by Dominik Kirst from Saarland University. It can be viewed as me carrying out one of the ideas mentioned in the &amp;ldquo;future work&amp;rdquo; section of my Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s thesis. Dialogical logic, originally put forward by Paul Lorenzen, captures the notion of first-order validity in terms of games modeled after a debate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications Peer-reviewed publications Material dialogues for first-order logic in constructive type theory: extended version
Dominik Wehr, Dominik Kirst
Mathematical Structures in Computer Science, November 2023. Exact bounds for acyclic higher-order recursion schemes
Bahareh Afshari, Dominik Wehr
Journal of Information and Computation, Volume 290, January 2023 Abstract Cyclic Proofs
Bahareh Afshari, Dominik Wehr
WoLLIC 2022, Iaşi, Romania, 2022. Material Dialogues for First-Order Logic in Constructive Type Theory [Preprint]
Dominik Wehr, Dominik Kirst</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Teaching At University of Gothenburg, I have taught the following courses:
Semester Course Position Spring 2023 Proof Theory Teaching assistant Fall 2022 Category Theory Course leader At University of Amsterdam, I was a student TA for the following courses:
Semester Course Spring 2021 Proof Theory At Saarland University, I was a student TA for the following courses:
Semester Course Summer 2019 Introduction to Computational Logic Summer 2018 Introduction to Computational Logic Winter 2017 Programming 1 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theses</title>
      <link>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/theses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dowehr.dortselb.st/theses/</guid>
      <description>Theses Representation Matters in Cyclic Proof Theory Type: Licentiate thesis
Supervisors: Graham E. Leigh and Bahareh Afshari
Digital copy: Available on GUPEA
A compilation thesis, consisting of two research articles, exploring cyclic proof theory from the perspective of proof representation, and an accompanying kappa.
More details here.
An Abstract Framework for the Analysis of Cyclic Derivations Type: Master&amp;rsquo;s thesis
Supervisor: Bahareh Afshari
Digital copy: Available on the ILLC eprints server</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
